ezbuy.sg 2017-06-06

# Most efficient, cost effective and reliable agent.

**What do we collect**

We may collect the personal details you submit on our site, such as name and email, mobile phone number, address, etc. Or other information we communicate by e-mail, telephone, live chat sessions, or alternate electronic or paper communication. 

**What do we do with the information we gather?**

We require this information in order to be able to provide our services to you, in particular for the following reasons: 

  * • Internal record keeping.  

  * • We may use the information to improve our services.  

  * • We may periodically send promotional news about changes to our services or special offers that we think you may find interesting, using the personal particulars which you have provided.  

  * • From time to time, we may contact you for market research purposes through the email which you have provided. Participation in our research is not mandatory and is completely optional.  

  * • We will never provide your information to third parties or sell your information.  

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online. 

**How do we use cookies**

Our website uses cookies in order to enhance your shopping and customer service experiences. By using our service, you are aware of and agree to our Terms of Service A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.   
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Cookies are also used by our online chat support system in order to save you from having to enter details every time you wish to use the system.   
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.   
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

ezbuy reserves the right to modify and change the Privacy Policy at any time provided the changes are published on our site. 

**Complaint about breaches of policy**

Please contact us as set below if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, any queries about our business practices, or any of your dealings with us, or our treatment of your personal information. Email: support@ezbuy.com
